export default  [
{
	"question": "24 / 4",
	"option1" : "4",
	"option2": "16",
	"option3": "6",
	"option4": "2",
	"answer": 3
},
{
	"question": "13 * 3",
	"option1" : "13",
	"option2": "203",
	"option3": "39",
	"option4": "63",
	"answer": 3
},
{
	"question": "9 - 0",
	"option1" : "5",
	"option2": "9",
	"option3": "0",
	"option4": "4",
	"answer": 2
},
{
	"question": "12 * 12",
	"option1": "134",
	"option2": "175",
	"option3": "152",
	"option4": "144",
	"answer": 4
},
{
	"question": "55 / 11",
	"option1": "5",
	"option2": "13",
	"option3": "36",
	"option4": "30",
	"answer": 1
},
{
	"question": "6 + 2 + 9",
	"option1": "10",
	"option2": "5",
	"option3": "17",
	"option4": "20",
	"answer": 3
},
{
	"question": "16 / 2",
	"option1": "20",
	"option2": "12",
	"option3": "43",
	"option4": "8",
	"answer": 3
},
{
	"question": "90 / 6",
	"option1": "17",
	"option2": "4",
	"option3": "9",
	"option4": "15",
	"answer": 4
},
{
	"question": "84 - 56",
	"option1": "16",
	"option2": "19",
	"option3": "27",
	"option4": "18",
	"answer": 4
},
{
	"question": "59 + 5",
	"option1": "62",
	"option2": "56",
	"option3": "46",
	"option4": "58",
	"answer": 1
}
]